ROBERT SMITH

IT Systems Administrator II

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

SUMMARY

Highly organized and highly self-motivated IT Systems Administrator with 2 years of experience in the Manufacturing domain. I enjoy building and maintaining a robust Information Systems, love to see technology be successfully implemented in a way that benefits the organization the only way that great solutions can.

CORE COMPETENCIES

BACKUPS, Network Security, IP Security Surveillance, VOIP, Firewall Configuration, Microsoft Office, Microsoft Exchange, ESXi/VMWare, Veeam Backup And Replication, ERP Upgrade Planning, Information Systems Infrastructure Auditing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

IT Systems Administrator II

Sourcecut Industries Inc - May 2016 - Present

Key Deliverables:

- Conferring with the network users about how to solve existing system problems.
- Analyzing the equipment performance records to determine the need for repair or replacement.
- Configuring, monitoring, and maintaining the email applications or virus protection software.
- Coordinating with the vendors and with company personnel to facilitate purchases.
- Designing, configuring and testing computer hardware, networking software, and operating system software.
- Diagnosing, troubleshooting, and resolving hardware, software, or other network and system problems.
- Implementing and providing the technical support for voice services and equipment, such as private branch exchange, voice.

IT Network Administrator Intern

Sourcut Industries Inc - December 2015 – April 2016

Key Deliverables:

- Assisted in the maintenance of computer hardware and software systems on the network including the maintenance and monitoring of active data network or converged infrastructure and related network equipment.
- Assisted with PC Administration in all levels of hardware and software support as needed, includes service desk support by answering calls, email and in-person user assistance, including but not limited to PC's, printers, scanners, and mobile devices.
- Worked with the technical team to provide support to key strategic projects and work assignments in the Infrastructure group.
- Created and implemented policies in order to comply with partners requirements.

ROBERT SMITH

IT Systems Administrator II

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

- Helped to perform a cutover of the existing network to a cloud-based network.
- Built and installed a high-performance network for 2 new buildings including over 30 access units, ethernet cabling and all necessary hardware.
- This is Dummy Description data, Replace with job description relevant to your current role.
 In case if you dont need it you can delete it.

EDUCATION

 Associates in IT Network Specialist - September 2014 to May 2016(Chippewa Valley Technical College - Eau Claire, WI) Diploma - 1996(Airport High School - West Columbia, SC)